<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<glossary lang="0">
	<entry id="0">
		<term>graph</term>
		<synonyms></synonyms>
		<definition>
			A mathematical structure consisting of nodes and edges.

			acyclic graph:
			A graph that does not contain any cycles.
			
			undirected graph
			A graph whose edges are undirected.
			
			directed graph (directed network, digraph)
			A graph whose edges are directed.
		</definition>
	</entry>

	<entry id="1">
		<term>node</term>
		<synonyms>vertex</synonyms>
		<definition>
			A part of a graph. Usually it has a name or value associated with it.
		</definition>
	</entry>

	<entry id="2">
		<term>edge</term>
		<synonyms></synonyms>
		<definition>
			A part of a graph, which does connect two nodes with each other.

			undirected edge:
			An edge whose direction is not determined and can be walked along in both directions.

			directed edge (arc, arrow):
			An edge whose direction is determined and can be walked along in just one direction.
		</definition>
	</entry>

	<entry id="3">
		<term>degree</term>
		<synonyms></synonyms>
		<definition>
			The number of edges that are adjacent to a node. It is used for undirected graphs more often, as the description with the in-  and out-degree is more precise for directed graphs.
			
			in-degree:
			The number of directed edges entering a node.
			
			out-degree:
			The number of directed edges starting from a node.
		</definition>
	</entry>

	<entry id="4">
		<term>sorting</term>
		<synonyms></synonyms>
		<definition>
			A sequence of objects sorted in a certain order.
			
			topological sorting:
			A sorting which sorts objects according to their dependencies on each other.

		</definition>
	</entry>

	<entry id="5">
		<term>algorithm</term>
		<synonyms></synonyms>
		<definition>
			A finite sequence of steps to solve a problem or a problem class.
		</definition>
	</entry>

	<entry id="6">
		<term>kahn’s algorithm</term>
		<synonyms></synonyms>
		<definition>
			An algorithm that performs a topological sorting on the nodes of an acyclic, directed graph.
			A node is only written to the output if its ancestor has already been processed. (and the algorithm that drives this simulation.)
		</definition>
	</entry>
</glossary> 
