<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<tutorial lang ="0">
<page number="1">
<headline>Node:</headline>
<body>
Here you can see a node (vertex). You can access it via the inventory on the left.
There are 5 types of nodes:
    - water 
    - vegetation/plants 
    - atmosphere 
    - plate tectonics 
    - moon 
Arranging nodes in certain combinations results in various changes to the planet. 
To arrange the nodes, all you have to do is drag it by holding your left mouse button and place it inside the graph editor. 
Once the nodes are arranged and connected with each other, you will see the in-degree in the top right corner of each node. 
</body>
</page>

<page number="2">
<headline>Inventory:</headline>
<body>
The inventory contains all available types of nodes to use 
and build your own graph. You may use each node as often as you like. 
    
To use a node from inventory, you simply have to 
drag and drop it from your inventory into the 
graph editor. To delete a node, just drag it back in the inventory. 
</body>
</page>

<page number="3">
<headline>Controls:</headline>
<body>
The control panel of the algorithm has three functions:
    - Start/Pause the algorithm (play)
    - Go to the next step (arrow to the right)
    - Repeat the last step (arrow to the left)

As soon as you built your graph, you are able to use the start button. 
Now the algorithm will run through your graph and build up your topological order.
The steps will be displayed on the console.

You also have the opportunity to delete all nodes at once by clicking on the bin
</body>
</page>

<page number="4">
<headline>Graph editor:</headline>
<body>
In this area you are able to build your own graph.
To build your graph, you can connect your created nodes with the right mousebutton.
To arrange your graph in a more structured way, you have 3 lines given.

Be careful not to include any cycles in your graph!
When you run the algorithm, the current node, which the algorithm is at and the node that will be visited are added to the output and marked visually.
Nodes that have already been visited and added to the output are also marked.
</body>
</page>
	
<page number="5">
<headline>Console:</headline>
<body>
The console displays the current state of your planet.
The planet gets updated with each step of the algorithm.
Moreover, each step will be documented here, as well as
the topologically sorted order the nodes of your graph are in during the algorithm's runtime.
</body>
</page>

<page number="6">
<headline>Settings:</headline>
<body>
Above the console, are a few controls.
Beside the buttons for controlling the audio output and starting/quitting the tutorial,
you will find a glossary as well as a button to switch the language of the game.
</body>
</page>

<page number="7">
<headline>Dynamic planet:</headline>
<body>
Right above the graph editor, you will find your planet, which will change its appearance depending on your graph as the algorithm runs.
Therefore, the order and quantity of your nodes affects the appearance of your planet.

In this way, the planet may change in its basic composition (lava planet, ocean planet, etc.) as well as in its atmospheric properties (sandstorms, thin atmosphere, etc.).
Moreover, moons may also appear in the orbit of your planet.
</body>
</page>
</tutorial>